That's what it's going to be called now.
We'll be getting into that. Um, Eric
Adams, they're trying to get him out of
the race. Uh, they're trying to bribe
him. It's probably not a feeling he's
unfamiliar with. We'll get into that.
Um, sanctions on Palestinians. Nothing
new there. This time it's for having the
timmerity to oppose genocide. We'll get
into the details there. Um, and this
part, I don't know if you care about
this, but you fly a lot. I I have a
feeling you do. Trump's decided to screw
uh airline passengers. And I wonder if
he's going to pay a price for that uh in
terms of populism, siding with the
airlines who are really kind of one of
the most hated industries in America
against ordinary passengers. But um
let's just get to it. What do you want
to talk about first, John?
>> I'd like to talk about Eric Adams first
if we could. Absolutely. only because
because you know deep down
deep down I still have a love of the of
the you know how the sausage is made at
the um
at the State Department and in foreign
policy. Uh
one thing about the Saudis and this is
why this is why Saudi Arabia is being
floated as a place for Eric Adams to end
up. The Saudis have always insisted
that they not have a career diplomat as
the US ambassador. They demand it, which
is exactly the opposite of most other
countries. The Saudis demand a political
appointee. Why?
>> Because they want to be able to pick up
the phone, call the ambassador, and have
the ambassador call the president, and
the president takes the call.
>> So, if you're a career diplomat, the
president's never heard of you. You
can't call the the White House in the
middle of the night and say, you know,
the the king of Saudi Arabia wants to
talk to you. So,
so as crazy as this might sound,
um the Saudis would be very happy to
have Eric Adams as the US ambassador.
That's not to say that 51 US senators
will agree to have Eric Adams as the uh
US ambassador. Although, if he were to
drop out of the race,
>> the Republicans endorse Quomo.
He'll still lose. But the Republicans
endors we need to break this down for
people who are not watching the details
of the New York City mayoral race, which
is super important even if you don't
live in New York or care about New York,
just because it's the epic showdown
inside the Democratic party between the
progressive left base of the party and
the corporist uh centrists who run the
DNC, right? uh you know so in the
primary uh Mumdani the Democratic
socialist basically a Bernie acolyte uh
managed to defeat um the a crowded field
and uh and is now in a general election.
He's the Democratic nominee current
polls I just checked the rear uh clear
politics averages as they currently
stand Zarron Mandani is uh 30 38.2% 2%.
Bringing up number two, a distant number
two, is Andrew Cuomo, former New York
ass grabbing governor. Um, he is running
as a third party candidate. Uh, I think
if I'm not mistaken, he's on the fan
fight anti-semitism
uh line. Subtle.
>> Yeah, it's like that. Um, Sydney
Wilkinson, the editorial cartoonist for
the Philadelphia Enquir, she has a
delightful
that she says in moments like that that
you just reminded me of. And uh, Curtis
Leewa, the uh, founder of the Guardian
Angels and the Republican nominee,
perennial Republican nominee, is at
16.6%.
Um, basically as popular as Lint is the
sitting incumbent mayor, Eric Adams, who
is currently uh, at 10.6%. 6%. So the
powers that be are looking at one
outlying poll that seems to indicate
that if you could get Adams and
hopefully Slewood to drop out, but
certainly Adams, you might actually be
able to beat Mamani with Cuomo. So the
billionaire class in the the real estate
um interests, Wall Street, all those
people. Uh that's their plot here,
right? So they're trying to clear the
field for Cuomo. Oddly, the New York
Post, which is the Murdoch Oregon here
in New York,
>> is still trying to push for Adams. I
mean, you know, honestly, Clovis, my
cat, has a far better chance of being
mayor than than Adams.
>> Seriously,
>> there's no way. I mean, no,
>> he's at 10.6% in the race.
>> The incumbent.
>> Yeah, that's right. Mdani is increasing
in the polls. Adams is has faced a lot
of very credible corruption charges. Um,
you know, I can't say that he's corrupt.
I mean, I think it's my opinion that he
is corrupt and takes bribes. Okay. Um,
but the and I think it's the opinion of
most New Yorkers, too. Um, but anyway,
so they're trying to get so they
basically the idea is, hey, let's get
rid of Adams. Adams drops out and
endorses Quomo.
>> Yeah,
>> we'll work on SWA. Slew says there is
absolutely nothing that uh he that can
convince him to drop out. He said they'd
have to be run over by a car to drop out
of the race.
So, and I say I kind of believe Curtis.
Um it it just seems very it's all very
desperate, right? And so, um, Steve
Witco, the, uh, Trump envoy, um, to
various middle, uh, you know, global hot
spots, including Russia, Ukraine, he's
floating this. We don't know how far
the, uh, food chain this has gone. We
don't know if the Donald is on board
with this or if he's just sort of, you
know, obviously he's reading about it.
Um, I don't know. I mean, how likely is
this?
>> You know what? I think
I think it actually is likely
because
Donald Trump's not stupid. I mean, we
like to criticize Donald Trump, sure,
but he's not stupid and he knows
>> his political instincts are obvious. I
mean, yeah, if this was a stupid man,
he'd be in jail right now. If he was if
he was a stupid man, he wouldn't be the
first person to be elected president
without military or political
experience.
not stupid.
>> Yep. He's not stupid. And so he knows
that Eric Adams isn't going to win this
race. He knows that there's not a prayer
for Eric Adams to win this race.
There's a better chance that Trump can
have um
have some serious input. If he gets
Adams out and so what do you do? You
offer him ambassador to Saudi Arabia.
Why not? That's going to make him happy.
And the Saudis want a political
appointee anyway. And um and then uh you
know, he at least throws a little bit of
a wrench into the Mumani campaign. Even
if Trump has already come to the
conclusion that Mani is going to win,
getting Eric Adams out of the race at
least forces Mumani to spend some money
and would allow people to then coales
around the candidate that Trump wants,
which is either well well it's or
neither Curtis Leewa nor um Andrew
Cuomo. It just makes it a little bit
tougher for Mum Donnie. I mean, Mommy's
he's already got the maximum number of
campaign contributions that he's allowed
to accept. People are throwing so much
money at him. So, I mean, it's hard it's
hard to see how he loses at this stage.
And he's increasing in the polls. He's
not going down. Um, the more that the
more that they pay attention to him, the
more that people like him in New York,
um, I I think all of this establishment
stuff is just, you know, not it it's
it's just it's it's counterproductive.
Yes.
>> Um, and it's it's just blowback, right?
Uh, I I don't know. I think it's going
to be it's super interesting to me to
see how this is all playing out. Um, and
I So, but I mean, I guess Eric Adams
gets a soft landing. How is that post
though? I mean, we talked yesterday
about, you know, the ambassadorial
position in Athens, which I think all
humans can agree is a nice job. How is
Riad I mean, you know, I you and I both
we have similar views on what it's like
to live in Saudi Arabia.
>> Yeah, I my own personal view is that
Saudi Arabia is the biggest open air
prison in the world. Um, but that's just
me. When I was serving in Saudi Arabia,
I served under two ambassadors there.
Um, one was Chaz Freeman,
the legendary Chaz Freeman, who, God
bless him, he's still alive. He has some
health problems, but he is one of the
leading voices out there in support of
the Palestinian people. Um, he went on
to be the assistant secretary of defense
and then he was supposed to be chairman
of the National Intelligence Council,
but the Obama people killed the
nomination because he's pro Palestinian.
So, the second one that I served under
um had been the governor of Mississippi
and then was Bill Clinton's Secretary of
the Navy. Nice guy, sweet guy,
completely out of his element. He just
did what he was told to do. Whoever
happened to be National Security Adviser
Sandy Burger for most of that period
just told him what to do and he did it.
That's what the Saudis wanted. So, if
you are the ambassador,
it's going to be good for you because
you're meeting with the king, you're
meeting with the crown prince, you're
meeting with the minister of foreign
affairs, you have the biggest uh parties
in the country, you have the biggest
mansion in the diplomatic quarter.
Life's going to be good. As soon as you
step out of that house, life's not going
to be so good because Saudi Arabia is a
terrible, terrible place to be. I would
rather be almost anywhere else than
Saudi Arabia.
>> Now, I imagine that that the ambassador
just like everywhere lives in a uh you
know, basically lives in a compound.
They can have alcohol. There's high
walls. They can pretty much do whatever
they want. They're living in their own
private Idaho, right? Like a wild
potato. Don't go on the patio. But but
isn't it
>> But so that's basically it. You're like
in your
>> You're in your Wall-E world. Yeah,
that's all. It's It's awful. It's awful.
And every once in a while, you get in
the car and you go over to Dahan and you
meet the people in the in the um uh
consulate there. And then you take a
quick flight over to Jedha. Uh the the
Saudi government, the entire government
moves to Jedha in uh in May. And they're
in May. They're in Jedha for May, June,
July, and August. And then the whole
government moves back to Riad because
Riyad's too hot. 120 125 degrees. So
they uh they just go to Jedha because
it's on the water and you get a little
bit of a breeze. It's still 120 degrees,
but I don't know. It's all relative, I
suppose. Uh but then that's it. The
reason why they want you in the first
place is they want to have somebody
who will have his phone calls taken by
the president. That's it. That's the
bottom line. Uh, Adam wants to know um
if is it true that if you want to work
in Saudi Arabia, you're appointed a
handler by the government, your passport
is taken away from you and you can only
leave with this permission.
>> Yes, that is true.
>> That is true. That's a serious human
rights problem.
>> Um,
>> yeah. Yeah, I should agree with that.
>> But yeah, you you have to be sponsored.
So, you have to say on your visa
application who your sponsor is. A Saudi
has to be the majority shareholder of
whatever company you're working for. So,
you can't just go to Saudi Arabia and
say, "I'm gonna open an LLC and we're
gonna make widgets." Uh-uh. You're gonna
open an LLC that you own 49% of. Some
random Saudi is going to own 51%. The
Saudi is going to hold your passport.
And if he doesn't like your face or you
have a fight or a falling out over
money,
then you're essentially under house
arrest because you can't go anywhere.
And that's how they that's how they keep
especially South Asian women as sex
slaves. They they hire them as
domestics, nannies, English teachers,
and then they arrive.
>> The sponsor takes the passport and says,
"Yeah, now take your clothes off and
you're going to be living in the
cupboard underneath the steps."
>> Lovely.
>> It's a great great place.
>> Best system. I hated it there.
>> Good thing we're so close to them. Um,
Marble wants to know and thanks for the
generous donation. Thanks also Houdini
and uh everyone else thoughts Marble
wants to know thoughts on Nigel
>> Farage for
Congress.
>> While you answered that, I'm going to
hit reboot. So don't panic. I'm just get
a better connection here.
>> You know, it's funny. As recently as
five years ago, Nigel Farage was was a
joke. He was like a kind of a neon-Nazi
fascist weirdo fringe weirdo from the
British rightwing.
And
just over the last 5 years with the
humiliation that the electoral
humiliation that the uh that the
conservative party underwent, Faraj has
come out as like a real voice on the
right. He's no less no less fascistic
than he was five years ago. He just has
been accepted by the mainstream as a
legitimate and this is nuts to me, but
as a legitimate right-wing voice. I I
when I was last in London, I was there
in March. Um there was a an article in
the Times of London. And the Times, of
course, it's a conservative paper and
it's owned by Rupert Murdoch and all,
but um there was a piece saying that
Nigel Farage um would likely be the next
leader of the Conservative Party. If
that happens,
I could see the end of the Conservative
Party as a viable political force.
>> Really?
>> Uh-huh. I think because because
conservatives who aren't that
conservative that they're called wets
the wetss
I think the wets would move to the
liberal party which is not liberal it's
actually quite conservative especially
on foreign policy and um I think that
the the ones who remain by the the Nigel
Farage uh uh
conservatives would just be sort of a
rump party.
Fared is a very interesting character
because
it sort of reminds me, not reminds me,
it reminds me of what I've read happened
in the UK in conservative politics in
the runup to the Second World War. There
were a lot of Brits who thought Hitler
was a-okay.
And a lot of those Brits, you know, it
took years for them to change Mosley
types.
>> Yeah, exactly right.
>> Yeah, people forget that the British
Fascist Party was a real thing.
>> It was a real thing and there were
members of the royal family that were
members of it.
>> Yeah. By the way, thank you so much uh
to Peter for becoming a monthly
supporter over Rumble. Much appreciated.
>> Um Okay. So, uh so, okay. So, let's talk
about the politics here. I mean, Trump
is going to I think, you know, I've got
to think that the reason Trump's not
allin on this plan is he knows that it
probably won't work and, you know, he
doesn't want to get behind a plan that's
likely to fail. That's right.
>> And then he'll be made fun of and he
hates that.
>> That's right. Yep.
>> So,
>> yeah, there are a lot of moving parts
here
>> and in the end, look at it this way,
too. Donald Trump does things that
benefit Donald Trump. So, how does this
benefit Donald Trump?
It doesn't really.
>> I mean, I would think that it would be
kind of I mean, look, I think that the
Republican party is planning to uh go
after Mumani as basically turn him into
their [__] for the next uh for the next
four years.
>> I I wouldn't be so sure it's going to
work. Um you know, he seems like a
really smart young man.
>> Yep. uh who's surrounding himself with
some uh older seasoned New Yorkers who
are going to hold his hand uh over at
Gracie Mansion and at city hall and
they're going to tell him how things
work. And I don't think he's just going
to go in there like a bull in a china
shop. I mean, he's been running [__]
great campaign.
>> I think you're right. Which is funny
because Ted, you remember
>> I mean, you remember better than I
You're a New Yorker. Um when Mumani uh
came out ahead,
so many on on the right, or not even
really on the right, in the center and
on the right said, "This is a fluke.
It's temporary. We're going to keep
running. Everybody's going to coales
around Quuomo and the DNC is going to
live happily ever after." And that's not
happening.
>> It's not.
>> No, not at all. Dan's mom political
godfather happens to be Jewish.
>> And so when people say, "Oh, Manny, it's
going to he's going to open ovens for
the Jews." And no, no, he's not.
>> No. And New York and New York voters,
many of whom are Jewish, are voting for
him, and they know they know they know
what he's about. That's right.
>> Um, you know, uh, so we we shall see. Uh
Nixon Barley says all of Amdany's
advisers are young. Guy is talking about
>> true.
>> Um his I got to tell you though um he
had that guy that God now his name is
escaping me who was uh running with him
uh who ran against him in the primary
and then endorsed him and they kind of
co-endors each other in the in the uh in
the primary. And that guy is like older
than we are and uh and he's holding
>> Yeah. I I I think I think that he hits a
big part of it. We'll see. We'll see. We
will see.
>> Hey, before we we move on to we we've
got a good question from Road Beef here.
If we mentioned Fudge, I must also ask
Ted and John for their opinion quickly
on Boris Johnson. Two peas in a pod. You
know, Boris I think there was nobody
there was nobody in the UK more shocked
when Boris Johnson became prime minister
than Boris Johnson.
He was a joke. Yeah,
>> he was a and not just a joke. He was a
he was a provocator journalist
um who made a a career
by pissing people off on purpose, right?
He was one of those original
I have an opinion right-wing journalists
and what are you going to do about it
kind of people.
>> Um but I think that he got into politics
just
just to troll people.
And one crazy thing led to the other and
then he found himself to be prime
minister. I will say another thing too.
Every time I go to the UK, I visit my
host family, the family that sponsored
me when I was 19 years old and I lived
with them and they are absolutely
wonderful, awesome people. My host
father was a member of parliament in the
1980s for the Liberal Party and um he's
in his late 80s now but uh but he is
still 100%
sharp and follows every detail of
politics. And he said this at the time
he said Boris Johnson never wanted to be
prime minister. He never intended to be
prime minister. This was all about just
lighting a fire under people and then
writing a book about it later and being
able to go on TV and promote yourself
and sell your book. He didn't think he
was going to actually be prime minister.
And then when he became
>> It's like Trump. There's a lot of dogs
that catch cars nowadays. It
>> it was about the branding for Trump.
Trump didn't think he was going to win.
This was about enhancing the brand. And
so, um,
so you find yourself prime minister of
the UK and you've been yelling about
Brexit, Brexit, Brexit for all these
months. You're going to have to leave
the European Union.
>> It's like, you got a Brex now.
>> You got a Brex. And
>> two great lines here uh from the from
this the um from the scroll. Uh Mdani,
Houdini says Mdani, regardless of what
he says during the campaign, if he wins,
he'll get the talk and fall in line.
Agreed. Just like AOC did. Uh and James
uh Gernales, this is like poetry, James,
youth and cunning will always be outdone
by age and treachery.
>> Amen.
>> That's if I had live in say that.
>> Yeah. Ugly world we live in.
>> It it it really really is. Uh John, so
let's see. Ross Houston wants to know,
"How valuable would access to a high
level member of the economy cabinet of
the UAE be to the CIA?"
>> Uh, not not very valuable. Um, the CIA
doesn't really spy on the UAE. There's
no reason to because they give us
everything that we want and we don't
really care about their economy. What we
care about most importantly in the UAE
is their commitment to the alliance with
the United States against Iran against
Iran and against the Houthis. Um we
don't we don't really care about the
economy besides
it's the Brits the Brits that make the
UAE economy run.
>> The Brits are all the bankers. The Brits
are all the advisers. They're managing
the the uh National Wealth Fund.
>> Yeah,
>> that's that's interesting. Um all right,
speaking of the talk, so if uh young
young bloodoods like uh like Mani get
the talk from the old school dudes who
tell them what's what. Uh I think you
know Trump has a boss too and that's the
corporations. Um Trump got uh is
obviously got a call from the airlines
CEOs and said don't you dare go ahead
with this last second Biden Buddha Jedge
plan that basically would have required
the airlines to pay you when not because
of weather but through some fault of
their own like their you know remember
when Southwest failed to upgrade their
computer systems and people got delayed
and I mean if you fly you know how
aggravating This is it happened to my
son recently. You know, he's changing
planes. The airline [__] up. He
doesn't make his connection. He's stuck
in a strange city. They're like, "Oh,
you can sleep in the airport overnight.
You can either do that or you can pay
shell out for, you know, a hotel at the
airport on your own dime and you got to
pay for extra meals and all that." Well,
in Europe, and I I have to say this is
an imperfect system, but in Europe, they
have a system where if the airline [__]
up, you can put in a claim and they have
to pay you. They have to compensate you.
Um Buddha Judge and uh outgoing Biden
pushed this through like too many good
things that they came up with, they did
in a cowardly way on the way out the
door. So, it never went into effect. And
now Trump is sort of quietly on a Friday
getting rid of this. Airlines are scum.
They make billions and billions of
dollars in profits. Um they are, you
know, squeezing us in. It's unsafe as
[__] to fly. I mean, if you ever I mean,
for me, okay, I'm 6'2. Um, you know, I'm
jammed in the seats, but that's not my
main concern. The deep the deep vein
thrombosis I can live and die with. But
like, you know, if you ever had to
evacuate the plane, which I've had to
do, you can't because there's no there's
no way to get past anyone. You you can't
the aisles are too narrow. I mean, it's
literally a safety issue. Um, and so
>> I mean, I just wonder this is such a
corporatist Reagan type move.
>> This is this is it's it's the kind of
thing that by itself it's not going to
be enough to destroy Trump's coalition.
But if you saw more and more of this, do
you think that we would lose people like
that? Trump would I mean, Trump's
already lost producer Robbie who voted
for him. But would he lose more people
like producer Robbie, more populist
conservatives um who are kind of like,
well, you don't care about the people.
You only care about the companies or or
are they just like not going to be aware
of it and not pay attention?
>> See, I think unfortunately it's the
latter. I think most people aren't
paying attention. And this is one thing
I really hate too is Americans have just
accepted the fact that it's okay to be
treated like cattle. I was in um
>> I was in Spain in like February or March
or something like that earlier this year
and I had to fly from Madrid to Dublin
and then Dublin to Washington. So, there
was a mechanical problem in Madrid and
uh finally they got the plane fixed and
they sent us to to Dublin, but I missed
my connection. It's not my fault I
missed the connection. Their plane was
broken. So, I went to the little desk
there, the information desk, and I said,
"Hey, you know, I was on this flight
from Madrid." "Oh, yes, yes, we've been
waiting for you. You're Mr. Kiryaku."
"Yes, I am." They said, "Yes. Um,
unfortunately there's not a flight to
Washington until tomorrow. So, we've
booked you in this four-star hotel
with buffet breakfast that could feed an
army and um your ticket was uh $1,200.
We're going to refund $600 of the
dollars. And I'm like, "Oh,
>> nice.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah,
>> great." So, I I went to the hotel. They
they had a a shuttle bus waiting to take
those of us that had to spend the night.
Took us to the hotel, expedited
check-in. It was a gorgeous hotel in the
center of Dublin.
Gigantic buffet. And then I went around,
did some sightseeing, and went back to
the airport the next morning and flew to
Washington. And then about six weeks
later, I got my $600 transferred into my
checking account. The craziest thing.
How come we don't do that?
>> Why are we held hostage? Look, I would
go further and say even when it's a
weather delay, there should be some form
of compensation. Um, pass I mean maybe
airlines can um charge an extra fund. So
it basically creates like a a
compensation fund so that when people I
mean it's it's okay. It's not the
airlines fault if there's a storm and I
don't want them to fly during a storm
but I mean you know
>> Sure. Sure. but people need to be able
to stay at the hotel at the airport.
Maybe you don't put them up at the
fourstar hotel, but they should be able
to go to the, you know, the Ramada or
the Marriott or whatever.
>> Yeah, totally agree. Everybody should do
this. The Europeans are so much
>> D. Wolson, thank you so much for
becoming a monthly supporter for us on
on Rumble.
>> Thank you.
>> Um, we are Robbie, go ahead and put that
ad up and I'll I'll go ahead and read it
when when you do. Um, so yeah, so I mean
this I mean it really b it it stuck in
my craw this news and I did notice that
it was happening on a Friday news dump
day uh you know sort of at a time of the
year when people are still like you know
spending a lot of time outside on the
weekend and I think you know they know
this isn't popular. I still maintain
that Pete Buddhaj Judge is the front
runner for the Democratic nomination in
2028, not Gavin Newsome. And this this
if I'm Pete Buddha Judge right now, I'm
doing a little dance, you know, because
I could say like, "Oh, I promoted this
and Trump killed it. I'm on your side.
Trump is on the airlines and the
corporations side." All right, here's
the ad.
>> Um, thanks everyone for listening to
this. Uh, if you haven't already, make
sure you down, make sure you download
the Rumble app. It's free, simple to
use, and the best way to stay connected
to the content you want once you've got
it. Search for my channel and hit follow
uh our channel. That way, you'll get a
notification every time we go live. No
missed shows, no extra steps. You can
grab it right now using the link in the
description or the pins live chat.
Download it to your phone and you're
ready to go. And if you prefer watching
on the big screen, Rumble is available
on all major streaming devices and smart
TVs. Just search for Rumble, follow the
channel, and be part of the action. And
indeed, please do watch us on Rumble
because that's where we make the the
financial action.
>> And I I want to say too, thanks to our
our viewers and to Robbie, we were on
the Rumble um
first page, front page, what do you call
it? the splash page, I think is what
they call it.
>> Splash page the other day. So, thank you
for watching us on Rumble. Um, it it
seriously boosted our viewership by a
good I'm going to say nine or 10%.
Um, and landed us on that front page.
So, thank you very much for that.
>> No, it's it's ins it's insanely very
much appreciated. Uh, the support has
been super inspiring. Um, Peter says,
"Every airport should have the words
from Dante's Divine Comedy inscribed,
abandon all hope, you who enter here,
you enter here."
>> It is a bleak [__] feeling when you
walk into an airport. You know, even if
you have TSA pre, it's going to be an,
you know, an undignified experience.
It's like, "Ah, we found your
applesauce, criminal." And
>> it's what a waste. I mean, I would
seriously get rid of TSA entirely. I
think it's a we could go back to the old
days where you can walk your walk your
loved ones to the gate.
>> I mean, seriously,
>> I told my son that the other day and he
thought I was kidding and I said, "No,
no, no. Everybody, the whole family just
parks the car and just walks in all the
way to the gate, hugs and kisses there."
When I was a little boy, when we would
figure when we would visit Washington
DC, visit relatives in Washington, my
dad used to always take me to national
airport. I remember I must have been
three or four. I still remember doing
this. And um there was an observation
deck on the roof of the terminal and you
could just watch the planes take off and
land. And for a little kid that was an
awesome thing.
>> Yeah.
>> You know,
>> it is awesome.
>> Now kids don't even they're like get out
of here. That never happened.
>> You want to This happened the following
thing happened in the early 90s. Uh my
uh my my my
sister-in-law had a she bought a two she
bought a roundtrip ticket. She couldn't
use the return.
I returned on her ticket. They didn't
even check my ID.
>> I did that once.
>> And you know what? And her name was
Alice. And literally the guy gives me a
funny look. I go, "You know, like Alice
Cooper." And he goes, "Okay."
>> Oh, okay. I bought my mom and dad
>> look just like Alice Cooper.
>> You may remember this this airline. It
was around for a minute. It was called
Bahamas Express and they had flights
from Kennedy to the Bahamas. So, you go
at 7:00 a.m., you arrive at like 9:30 in
the morning in the Bahamas. You hang out
on the beach all day. You go shopping.
You have lunch, whatever. You get back
on the plane at 5 and you land in New
York at like 8 and it was $99.
>> That's awesome. So, for my mom and dad's
30th anniversary, I bought them two
tickets to the Bahamas on Bahamas
Express, not knowing that my dad had
already bought tickets for them to go to
Greece.
>> Oh.
>> So, I'm stuck with these two
non-refundable tickets. And in, you
know, 19 whenever it was, no, it wasn't
their 30th.
It must have been their 20th.
Um cuz I was I was 18.
Well, $200 is a lot of money.
>> Oh, yeah. Especially back then,
>> 1982.
>> Sure [__] was. Yeah.
>> And so I said to my brother, I said,
"Hey, you want to go to the Bahamas?
Just the two of us. We'll go down for
the day. We'll drink and party and go to
the beach, whatever." He's like, "Yeah,
my mom's name is Stella, right?"
>> So I hand the guy the ticket and he
looks
>> not like Alice Cooper. There's no
rockers. No one named Stella.
>> He looks at the ticket. He looks at me
and I'm just standing there looking at
him and he says to me, I'll never forget
it. He says, "Buddy, $50 name change fee
next time." And I said, "Okay."
Got on the plane
>> and nothing happened. No terror.
>> No. Everybody was happy and and my
brother and I have some great pictures
to remember our day in the Bahamas. And
don't forget TSA
did not well TSA didn't exist. The
predecessor to TSA,
>> right?
>> Yeah. Those box cutters were legal to
bring on. Totally legal.
>> Yes.
>> You know, so
>> yeah. I mean, I don't know. I mean, I
know I think security matters, but I,
you know, John, have you ever What do
you make of the fact that, you know, you
have to basically go through an anal
probe to get onto a plane,
>> but a train is no problem or a bus. You
just get on. I'm always amazed by that.
>> They all arrive. They they I don't think
there's any more terrorist attacks. I'm
Has there ever been a terrorist attack
against a train in the United States?
The last time I can think of one was
like the um the South Malucas terrorists
in Holland in like the 1970s, like
hijacked a train. It like never happens.
>> Carlos the Jackal killed a handful of
French policemen on a train in the 70s
>> at some point. But no. And Ted, you and
I both travel by train with some
frequency. I mean, we we live on the
East Coast. It's really the only way to
get between Boston and Washington. I do,
too. I love trains.
>> And um
>> not only do they not have security,
>> they don't even look at the ticket until
you're on and the train's already going.
Like, you don't have to show an ID,
nothing. You just get in line, get on
the train.
One time recently, Beautiful. It's a
beautiful thing, John. Just I mean, and
the bus you can get on any, you know,
Greyhound doesn't care. I mean,
>> Bolt Bus doesn't care. No one cares.
>> No, Bolt doesn't care at all. No. What?
This this uh trip where my flight was uh
delayed and I missed
>> Houdini's right. There was that attack.
There's a little there's a movie about
it that was thwarted by the US airmen uh
on this on the TGV.
>> Oh, that's right. You know what? I
should remember that because the hero
was Greek American and he was like on
the front page of all the Greek papers.
>> MW Knox wants to know, do we prefer the
uh the pruno the pronuno scanner or the
pat down?
>> Um
>> uh I'll take the scanner. I hate when
people strangers are touching me like
that.
>> Uh I do not I don't I don't do the uh
you know by the way at the airport now
they have this thing. It's really
freaky.
>> Um where they they they they say, "Oh,
stand over here and we'll take your
photo."
>> Yeah.
>> For facial recognition.
>> Don't like it.
>> And you don't have to say yes. It's
optional.
>> But they basically say when you step up
there, they don't say you don't have to
do it. They say step over here.
>> Yep.
>> And in front of the camera. And you have
to say I, you know, I decline. They're
like, "Oh, you decline." I mean, it's
not like they give you a really hard
time, but you know, they clearly don't
like it.
>> No, they don't like it. But you can
decline. It'll delay you just a couple
of minutes, but you can you can decline.
>> I had a I had a friend journalist
currently at the New York Times flew out
of Tel Aviv. Um, and he was he had just
he worked on a kabutz, you know, as
Jewish as the day is long. Joint
citizenship in Israel. He's flying back.
He's flying alone. So ll they decide to
give him they literally were like, "We
need to do a body cavity search."
>> What?
>> And uh and I was like, "You mean?" And I
was joking. I'm like, "So, including
your anus?" He's like, "Yeah." And I'm
like, "So, what did you tell him?" He
goes, "Well, I didn't want to miss my
flight." I go, "Are you kidding me?" I
would have been like, "Fuck you. Call
the call the US embassy." And it's like,
it's like, "Oh, but I would have missed
my flight." I've been like, "I'd missed
my flight for a week. Those people
aren't sticking their fingers out my ass
if I can help."
>> No way. No. I got strip searched in
Iceland in December. Um, down to my
underwear and I was boiling, raging mad,
but I never spoke a word. Never said a
word. I didn't want to give them the
satisfaction.
>> What would have happened if you declined
or refused?
>> I think they probably would have told
me, "Turn around and leave the airport."
And there's no other way to get out of
Iceland. You're kind of stuck.
>> Miserable miserable place. Yeah. That's
just terrible.
>> OMG.
OMG. Oh, Jen wants you to finish your
story. I don't know. Did I interrupt
you? I apologize.
>> Yeah, that Oh, that's okay. What story
was I Jen? What was I talking about?
>> Sorry. I do that. I get I get over
enthusiastic.
>> I don't remember what we were talking
about. We were talking about trains. Jen
Jenners.
>> She'll put it up. She she's a she's a uh
she's a she's a she's a follower a
frequent follow follower so she has to
exc remember
>> um okay so we have a we did Eric Adams
um we we should probably talk about the
well we have to do the war department
>> yeah we have to you know what call me
crazy but it is a federal
a federal
>> it was your train story Jenna saying
Sorry.
>> Yeah, I don't remember what I was saying
about the train.
>> I'm sorry. If you think of it, let me
know and I'll finish it.
>> Right.
>> So, um,
>> war department.
>> Yeah, it is. It is a war department.
>> It it was the department of war until
1947 and President Truman uh changed it
because it sounded kind of wararmongery.
Um, and but it is it is.
>> What was it about World War I mean, it's
weird that I mean, I don't know the
politics of this. Why did Truman change
it in 47? I mean, we just won World War
II. Everyone loves us. I mean, was it
just what was the point?
>> He didn't want to be seen. He didn't
want the United States to be seen as as
a an aggressor, as an imperialist.
And so, um,
and so he changed it to defense. But
listen, we're all we're all relatively
moderately, you know, intelligent
people. We can tell the difference
between defense and offense. And we're
an offensive uh military country really
since since we achieved, you know,
so-called superpower status at the end
of the Second World War. Um we invade
countries all over the globe.
>> Hundreds
>> all over the place. We're overthrowing
governments. We're invading. We're
occupying it is a department of war. So
we're invading airspace.
>> I have no problem with this change. He
signed he I'm sorry. Let me finish this
thought. He signed a an executive order
uh he announced it last night. He signed
the executive order today mandating the
change. A president can't change the
name of a federal department. It has to
be an act of Congress.
>> Do you think Democrats will go along
with it or do they actually do you need
it's just is it a simple majority vote?
>> Simple majority. You need 60 in the
Senate because you have to break
closure. But I mean, there's so many
more important things to worry about. I
I don't think the Democrats are going to
care one way or the other. I wouldn't,
but they may oppose it just to make life
harder for Trump and for the
Republicans.
>> Well, you know, right about this.
>> Pacifists have been saying for years
that it should be called the War
Department.
>> So, I'm wondering what they're going to
say about it. You know, I mean, it is
more accurate. Um, I have no problem
with it at all. I mean, definitely
Trump's statement yesterday was
hilariously incipid where he's like,
"Defense sounds too defensive. We also
have to be off offensive." And I'm like,
"Don't worry, Donald. You're always
offensive." Um, but it's just so like
dumb. But yeah, I'm totally fine with
it. Um, you know, no problem. I just
wonder if it's going to maybe backfire
in the future and make it a little more
difficult for uh you know the defense
appropriations to always get rubber
stamped year after year after year.
Sorry, the war appropriations.
>> Hey, I I want to ask you too, we have a
question here. It's an important one. Uh
first of all, my good sir, thank you
very much for that $10. He says, "Can
you uh please cover the breaking story
about US Marines going into North Korea
and killing North Korean civilians?" Oh
yes.
>> To me, this is a huge story. It is a
huge story. And I want to read to you
Trump's response.
>> Uh Trump was asked
>> um if the administration had engaged
with North Korea since this happened in
2018. It it's a story broken by the New
York Times. And listen to this response.
Quote, "I don't know anything about it."
No, I'd have to. Well, I could look, but
I know nothing about it. I don't know
anything about it. I'm hearing it now
for the first time. First of all, liar,
liar, pants on fire. We're not going to
send Seal Team Six into North Korea for
a botched operation where they start
shooting civilians. And the president
didn't know anything about it. That's
not how covert operations work. Not only
did the president have to know about it,
he had to physically sign a paper called
a finding
authorizing special forces to do
something like this. So, he's lying.
>> So, to bring people up to date in case
you're not you didn't follow this piece
in today's New York Times, John, correct
me if I get any of the details wrong.
Um, I'm just doing this by memory, but
in 2019,
>> 2018, at the time when relations with
North Korea and the US were sort of
thawing, um, and the US thought and
Trump thought was hoping there could be
a ruproma, they wanted to learn more
about Kim's thinking. And they thought
we need we they have a device that would
allow them to uh eaves drop on Kim's
communications. But the catch was that
the device had to be planted on North
Korean soil or it wouldn't work. So,
Seal Team 6 was assigned this task. Um,
they planned it out well and practiced a
lot, but it it didn't go well. And
basically when the weather was a little
off, um, the landing didn't go quite
right. And basically they and the water
was super cold, the conditions were
hard. Um, and basically, uh, while they
were trying to do it, a they saw a North
Korean boat arrive and they nobody spoke
Korean and they couldn't hear what they
were saying anyway. They thought it was
kind of like, "Look, there's something
going on." And so anyway, they they they
uh aborted the operation, shot the
people on board who turned out to be
fishermen,
>> killed everybody.
>> Killed everybody. killed everybody on
the boat
>> and and and screwed the pooch and took
off, right? And didn't and didn't manage
to plant the device. And the New York
Times got this information and basically
in the context of apparently Sealed Team
6 and groups like it often have botched
operations and they tend to brag about
their successes but the you know the
failures don't get much PR and this was
one of them and Trump had to personally
sign off because it was so risky uh that
you know they were worried about you
know being they could be caught on they
could have been captured or killed.
on North Korean soil. So, it would have
been a huge embarrassment and a massive
international incident.
>> Huge. And listen, there was a serious
violation of protocol on the part of the
White House, too, because
the law says that that the White House
has to inform
at least the gang of four, if not the
entire committee on both sides. the gang
of four being the chairman and vice
chairman of the Senate Intelligence
Committee and the House Intelligence
Committee. If it's so sensitive
that you want to keep it, you know, eyes
only, you do the gang of four. And they
didn't inform the committees either
before or after the operation.
I mean, heads should have rolled and
nothing happened. May I add to Hello
Aasam says, "John, yesterday you
mentioned Afia Sadiki. Can you tell us
more about her, please? And thank you.
You know, thanks for that. Do we have a
minute, Ted?
>> Absolutely.
>> Um, so I I had Afia Sadiki's attorney
over at my house today for coffee and um
and we recorded an episode of of my uh
Deep Focus podcast talk about Afia
Sadiki. Afia Sadiki was a Pakistani
American um uh neurosurgeon
uh with a PhD from Brandeise and a
bachelor's degree from MIT. Woman was
absolutely brilliant. Her sister also is
a PhD
uh like neurologist or neurosurgeon or
something like that.
Um, Afia self-radicalized
right around the time of the World Trade
Center uh and Pentagon attacks 911 and
she went back to Pakistan and she
volunteered to join al-Qaeda.
So, we capture Khalik Muhammad in August
of 2002, I think is what it was, and he
said, "Oh, there's this woman Afia
Sadiki. She's really bad. I'm I'm
ratting her out." Uh, you need to grab
her. Well, we found her in Karach and we
grabbed her. We asked the Pakistanis to
grab her. They gave her to us and we
took her to Afghanistan and locked her
up. Here's the rub. She had three young
children at the time, a boy, a girl, and
a young boy who was uh an infant.
And as it turns out, well, before I tell
you how it turns out, she was turned
over from the Pakistanis to the Afghans,
from the Afghans to the Americans, and
the FBI flies out to begin interrogating
her. Here's where the stories all
diverge.
The official story is
that she was in a tent waiting to be
interrogated.
One of the FBI agents had an M4.
He leaned his M4 up against the side of
the tent. She grabbed it. She tried to
shoot him. The gun jammed. And another
FBI agent took out his gun and shot her
twice in the stomach. Um, she survived.
That's the official
version. Um, she went on to be charged
with attempted murder and she was found
guilty and given 86 years in prison.
She didn't murder anybody. She didn't
even injure anybody. So, he told me this
is the longest sentence ever given in
American history to someone for
attempted murder where there was no
discharge of a weapon.
86 years. The story gets worse.
In the um during the trial,
they uh showed
bullet holes, two bullet holes in the
canvas of the tent, and they said, "See,
she got two shots off. We had to shoot
her." But as it turned out, they had
been interrogating prisoners in that
tent for for months. and and another
photograph surfaced showing the bullet
holes were already in the canvas of the
tent weeks before Afia Sadiki was ever
caught. So, no, she did not fire the
shot. She didn't fire any shots. Here's
what makes this case even worse.
The CIA kidnapped all three of her
children and they turned them over to
Christian missionaries in Kabell.
The eldest son was adopted by a
missionary family and they changed his
name.
The middle child, a daughter, was
adopted by another missionary family and
they changed her name.
No one ever figured out what happened to
the baby.
So
the war ends
and Hamid Cararzi who was president of
Afghanistan is placed under house
arrest. My friend um the attorney went
to Afghanistan. He's befriended the
Taliban government. He told them what
happened. Afia Sadiki is a giant hero in
both Pakistan and Afghanistan. And so he
said, "I really need to talk to Hamid
Carzi." So the Taliban tells Cararzi,
"You're going to talk to this British
human rights lawyer." And Cararzi's
like, "Yeah, we we snatched the kids. We
turned them over to the CIA. They just
farmed them out for adoption."
He found the kids
and um they're adults now, but he's
reunited them with Afia Sadiki's sister
in Pakistan. They now live with her.
the baby would now be 18 years old. And
the only news that he's been able to get
about the baby
um was
verbal and it was that that the baby had
been dropped on his head and he was
killed.
>> What?
>> And he says, "I think that's complete
and total [__] The CIA just doesn't
want us to know where the baby is." The
baby, like I said, is now 18. So what he
did is he got Afia's sister to give a
DNA sample
and he registered it with 23 andMe and
GED match and um you know all these
different you know ancestry.com.
He also used AI to age the picture of
the baby to what he would look like at
the age of 18 today. and um
and he said, "We're we're trying to find
him."
And so now he's he's suing the CIA,
which of course is going to go nowhere.
Um he's suing the FBI, which is going to
go nowhere. and he said, "Look, I I know
we're not going to win any of these
suits, but I'm hoping that the suits
garner enough public attention that some
18-year-old dark-skinned kid out there
is going to say, "Maybe this is me
they're talking about and that he does a
a DNA test." So, I said, "Well, what
about Afia? She's going to die in
prison. She's at She's at FMC Carwell,
which is a maximum security medical
prison. She's in solitary confinement
and has been in solitary confinement
since 2008.
He told me that she has for all intents
and purposes lost her mind. And of
course the prison doctors say um yeah,
she's faking that craziness. It's not
from being in solitary confinement for
the last 17 years. She's just faking it.
He told me that on Thanksgiving
she was given a plate of food with
turkey, potato stuffing and corn and
some pumpkin pie and she let it sit and
they asked her why she didn't eat her
Thanksgiving dinner. And she said, "No,
no, she's saving it for her son because
he must be so hungry by now." And they
wrote it up. They said, "She's faking
this PA PTSD. She said that she's
waiting to feed her son and everybody
knows her son is dead."
So I said, "Well, what what can we do?"
And he said, "She does respond to um to
letters."
Um he answers, his name is um is Clive
uh Stafford Smith. Uh
hold on one second. I'm going to find
him. There he is. He's Listen to what an
awesome guy he is. He's a He's a member
of the um Order of the British Empire.
the queen, Queen Elizabeth gave him an
OBBE
uh because of the work that he's done on
human rights. He has never charged a
client a single dollar in all of his
life. Um he just lives on donations.
He's devoted he's he's represented 66
Guantanamo detainees and he's gotten
every one of them released. All 66.
and um he says to write to him. It's
it's Clive Stafford Smith2020gmail.com.
He will deliver the um the letters to to
Afia. But he said her only hope is that
President Trump commutes her sentence
and lets her go home to Pakistan. And
that's not going to happen.
John, I I hate to bring this up, but we
do have some breaking news. Um uh also,
I should probably uh we have another ad.
So, Robbie, whenever you're ready. Uh
but first, I'll break this. So, a
federal judge has blocked uh Christine
Nome and the Trump administration from
getting rid of those temporary Biden era
protections for the Venezuelans and
Haitians that they're trying to deport.
Uh the judge was extremely um uh upset
with the administration. US District
Judge Edward Chen said that Christy
Gnome illegally stripped that status in
a truncated and condensed timeline that
did not follow the law. So um another
defeat in court for the Trump
administration, but I think they they
see that coming. Let me read this ad.
Quick pause to tell you about Pickax,
the creator and user first platform
built for people, not algorithms. You
know what big tech is up to. Data
mining, bot driven feeds, blackbox AI
deciding who sees your work. Instead,
Pickax hands you an algorithm free
chronological feed with native Rumble
playback, autopublishing of your live
streams, free blue check verification,
and full monetization control. Your
voice, your rules. Best of all, the web
version is live right now and their iOS
and Android apps drop next month. On
Pickax, your Rumble videos play
seamlessly right in your feed as if they
were built into the platform. No embeds,
no workarounds, just smooth native
playback. Even better, in beta now,
creators can connect their Rumble
channel to Pickax to automatically post
live streams and videos so your
followers never miss a moment. We'll
have to do that. You can also write full
articles directly on Pickax today. In
fact, I did that today. And later this
year, you'll be able to blast them out
as well as email newsletters with one
click and build up your own email list
for direct audience access. Monetize on
your terms through pay walls, revenue
sharing, or affiliate ads that
autoinsert promo codes and tracking
links. And because bots shouldn't steal
your spotlight, Pickax hands you a free
blue check so everyone knows it's really
you. Pickax is building tech that builds
up humanity algorithm free, noise free,
human first. Head to pickaxe.com, sign
up, and take your platform to the next
level. Real voices deserve a real home.
>> I like that.
>> John, what what about this court? latest
court thing. I mean, obviously the Trump
administration is used to this. They do
what they want. They then they know that
while they're doing it, uh the courts
are slow. The courts will get around to
it. When they lose, which they do, they
appeal. They they appeal. And I guess
they kind of their ace in the hole is
the Supreme Court, which seems to be
really supplicant.
>> Yeah. Um I agree with you. I think this
is this is the strategy. The strategy is
do anything you want and let them sue
you. Um, and so they lose what 50% 60
70% of the time, whatever, but they do
what they do in the interim and then in
the end they they win a couple.
So yeah, I think it's the policy. I
think that they fully intend or fully
expect rather to lose and they say, "Ah,
we don't care. We're just going to do
what we want."
>> Indeed.
Yeah. Oh, can I add one one last thing
about Afia Sadiki? Somebody's asking me
what was her side of the story. Her side
of the story was actually quite
believable.
>> Um,
her side of the story was she was
sitting uh in a chair in the tent. When
the FBI agents arrived, she heard them
speaking English and she said, "Oh, the
Americans are finally here." Thinking
the Pakistanis snatched her, turned her
over to the Afghans. the Americans are
going to save her and protect her.
>> And so she says, "Oh, the Americans are
here." So she got up, she took off her
veil,
looked through the slit in the tent, a
soldier said, "She's trying to escape."
And he shot her twice in the stomach.
That's her side of the story, which is
very believable to me.
[Music]
Well, while we're talking about
>> 86 years in prison,
>> that's some [__] And while we're
talking about some [__] uh the
Trump administration just imposed
sanctions against three Palestinian
groups, the Palestinian Center for Human
Rights, Al-Hawk and Al-Mazan,
uh for having the timmerity to ask the
International Court uh criminal court to
look into alleged Israeli war crimes in
Gaza. Uh these are Marco Rubio's
sanctions. His complaint was that they
they asked the IC to get involved and
look into this without getting Israel's
consent. John.
>> Ah,
okay.
>> So, next time I'm pulled over for
speeding, I'm going to file a complaint
against the police officer for not
getting my consent.
>> Yes.
>> To pull me over.
>> And to and to to fire that radar gun at
me. Well, if you watch YouTube videos,
>> don't I deserve Don't I deserve to say
>> and if you watch YouTube videos, you
know that what you have to do is just
start screaming, "I do not consent." as
soon as they come up to your to your
window,
>> right?
>> Because that always works.
>> Yeah. You You're making friends. They
love that.
>> Right.
>> There you are in the middle of
Interstate 80 between like Clarion and
Clearfield and they're they're loving
that. Yeah.
>> Oh my god.
Yeah.
>> So, I mean, it's just that the Israelis,
I mean, they've lost it. They've
completely lost their minds.
>> When When
are we going to be able to finally call
the Israelis on their on their [__]
I I'm not optimistic.
>> I actually am. I just I mean, I guess
it's too late to be optimistic because
so many people have already died
horribly. Um, so it is too late for
that. But honestly, I do think it's
inevitable. And I think it's going to be
it's either going to be Trump or someone
like him. It's going to be someone
>> who who normally is always in the bag
>> and it's just going to say like, you
know, Lindsey Graham, like enough,
right?
>> Just like it may probably won't be
Lindsey Graham, but you know, someone
who's just it's going to come out of
left field. It'll be like when France
recognized Palestine when suddenly it's
just like the damn the damn bursts.
That's what it's gonna be like.
>> I think you're right.
>> Well, um let's see. Do we have any uh I
guess that's about it right for today.
Uh JD Vance Houdini says that's a good
guess actually.
>> A really good I'm serious.
>> Yes.
>> I mean JD Vance is we know he'll change
his mind.
>> Oh yeah.
>> Democrat. Ah, I'm a Republican. I'm an
anti-Trump Republican. I'm a proTrump
Republican.
>> Uhhuh.
>> You know, he'll be anything you want him
to be.
>> That's right.
>> I think that's right.
>> All right, guys. Well, this is that's it
for uh an awesome week. By the way, um
guys, if you haven't listened to uh if
you're not Rumble Premium, you got to go
to Rumble Premium or think about being
Rumble Premium just to check out John
and uh producer Robbiey's uh I
interviewed both of them. Robbie's story
is amazing. John's obviously amazing. Uh
we've we've dropped three hour three
episodes about an hour each. Um where I
interviewed him about his life story and
we probably going to be doing two more
maybe maybe three more. Who knows? I
mean just you know we're we're taking
>> I apologize in advance as I told Ted
yesterday.
>> I have w No, there's no apologies
allowed. Um and honestly it's just
amazing. Uh, you know, it's a privilege
to do them and, uh, you know, I I sent
the links to a few friends and they
loved them. So,
>> Oh, great.
>> Uh, so yeah. So, definitely check that
out. Um, John, do you have a website you
want to pimp? Um, I'll
>> Sure. You know what? I have It's
johncuryaku.com. We're going to
seriously beef it up soon. Um, for a
couple of reasons. Well, you know what?
I'm going to spill the beans. I'm going
to spill the beans. They told me I could
if I wanted to. I am finally gonna
appear on the Joe Rogan podcast.
>> Woohoo.
>> On October 9th. Thank you. And um
and I'm thinking that with his 18.9
million subscribers, that might drive a
little bit of traffic to the
>> 1% of them. That's true.
>> I'm going to talk about Deep Program and
Deep Focus, but I'm also expecting to
start to restart my speaking tour um in
December. And so I gotta have that
website like perfect. It's decent now,
but uh but it's got to be perfect.
>> Rald.com for me, cartoons, columns, and
everything else. I have a Substack, Ted
RAW.substack.com.
>> My latest book is called What's Left?
And it's a basically a prescription for
what the left, the real left, not the
Democratic Party, should be asking for
domestically and in terms of foreign
policy. Um anyway, really appreciate it.
You get you can get those on my website
raw.com, Amazon, order it from your
local bookstore, whatever. Okay, guys.
Thank you so much for tuning in as
always. Super appreciated. Thank you,
producer Robbie West, as always. Oh,
Putinbot Gaming. Go check it out um on
go check out that gaming channel. Um it
help it helps him and helping him helps
us. So, Robbie's keeping this whole
thing going. Robbie, I'm popping Robbie
on here. There's Robbie. Howdy.
>> Say something.
>> Say something about Putinbot Bait
Gaming.
>> Yeah, I'm on YouTube and Rumble. Uh, if
I'm a part of the Rumble content creator
program, so if I'm on if I'm live, if
y'all just pop over, say howdy or call
me any kind of name that you want.
There's a chat metric that's involved
and I'll stream as much as I as I used
to because well, I'm here. So, if y'all
could do that, it would just help me out
a lot. And um I've already told John and
Ted that they're out of work and I'm
not. So, I'm doing this for free. So, uh
if y'all can come over and throw some
watch hours my way, I'd appreciate it.
Thank you.
>> Oh, watch our Discord server.
>> Have a great weekend, everyone. Take
care. Thanks for watching Drogram. We're
back next week, Monday, 5 o'clock
Eastern time. We're here Monday through
Friday, 5:00 Eastern. Like, follow and
share the show. Watch us on Rumble. Bye.